A Guide to the Thomas Gordon Pollock Papers
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Thomas Gordon Pollock Papers 1838-1921, n.d.
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
8458,-a,-b
This collection consists of ca. 210 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This material was given to the library by W. Hugh Peal on December 20, 1966 (#8458); April 13, 1967 (#8458-a); and October 6, 1969 (#8458-b).
Scope and Content Information
This collection consists of ca. 210 items, 1838-1921, and n.d., chiefly pertaining to Thomas Gordon Pollock.
Contents List
- Correspondence of the Pollock Family
  - Correspondence of Abraham David and Elizabeth Gordon (Lee) Pollock 1838-1884
    8458
  - Correspondence of Charles Lee Pollock and Lily Pollock 1887-1888
  - Correspondence of Thomas Gordon Pollock with his brother, Charles Lee Pollock, and his sisters 1852-1863
  - Letters from Abraham David and Elizabeth Gordon (Lee) Pollock to their son, Thomas Gordon Pollock 1857-1861
  - Letters from Thomas Gordon Pollock to his parents, Abraham David and Elizabeth Gordon (Lee) Pollock (2 folders) 1852-1863
- Letters to Thomas Gordon Pollock, and related
  - Letters from Edward C. Anderson, Jr. to Thomas Gordon Pollock 1859-1861
  - Letters from M[ ] Boyce to Thomas Gordon Pollock 1860-1861
  - Letters from Douglas F. Forrest to Thomas Gordon Pollock 1858-1859
  - Letters from Thomas Gordon Pollock at the request of S. D. Moore 1860
  - Letters from Meriwether Lewis Randolph to Thomas Gordon Pollock 1860
  - Letters from John Scott to Thomas Gordon Pollock 1859-1861
  - Letters from Robert I. Taylor Scott and E. G. Scott to Thomas Gordon Pollock 1856-1859
  - Letter from Henry A. Wise to Meriwether Lewis Randolph, Thomas Gordon Pollock, and T. K. Baker 1859
  - Letters to Thomas Gordon Pollock 1858-1861
- Topical
  - Biographical Sketch of Thomas Gordon Pollock 1869
  - Lee Monument 1890-1893
  - Legal Papers of Thomas Gordon Pollock 1860-1861
  - Obituaries of Abraham David Pollock and Charles Lee Pollock, and miscellaneous newspaper clippings 1888, 1890
  - Papers of Charlotte, Margaret, and Nancy Lee 1908-1910, n.d.
  - Photograph of "Leeton Forest," Pollock family home in Fauquier County, Virginia 1897
  - Writings of the Pollock Family n.d.
  - Claim: Hudson of U.S. Geological Survey vs Isthmiam Canal Commission 1904
    8458-a
  - Claim: Skillman et al. vs Daniel et al. [1901]
  - Claim: Southern Railway Company vs Eppa Hunton, Jr. 1903
  - Correspondence of John Janney re The Mutual Life Insurance Company of New York 1901
  - Miscellaneous n.d.
  - Notes on Law and Notes on Evidence 1904, n.d.
  - Correspondence of the Pollock and Janney families 1846-1921
    8458-b